<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on B&#39;Log</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on B&#39;Log</description>
    <image>
      <title>B&#39;Log</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/pics/billxbfc.png</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pics/billxbfc.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beneath Agentic Sandbox</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sandbox-agent-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sandbox-agent-design/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Modern AI agents are often scaffolded with a runtime sandbox. Often referred to as Computer-Use Agents (CUA), they autonomously run code, use terminal, take notes, and access Internet and MCPs &amp;ndash; exactly like humans do when interacting with the digital world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yet, the reasoning and best practices remain unclear to most. So let&amp;rsquo;s dive into popular agent scaffolds like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.anthropic.com/engineering/claude-code-best-practices&#34;&gt;Claude Code&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://agent.minimax.io/&#34;&gt;MiniMax Agent&lt;/a&gt;, demystifying the design principles and discovering how agents benefit from using a computer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I start to write</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a fairly procrastinated start to my personal blog. Starting a blog isn’t as easy as it seems—I don’t want to waste people’s time with casual anecdotes. Meanwhile, an overly formal academic write-up would likely be overkill and scare people away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are many people who truly enjoy machine learning and find joy in sharing knowledge. I’ve been a long-time follower of AI/tech blogs from &lt;a href=&#34;https://karpathy.github.io/&#34;&gt;Andrej Karpathy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://lilianweng.github.io/&#34;&gt;Lilian Weng&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://yaofu.notion.site/&#34;&gt;Yao Fu&lt;/a&gt;, and others.
I usually prefer blogs over papers because blogs feel more honest and less AI-polished (or written to attract citations). Yet almost everyone I followed stopped posting in early 2025. I understand the shifts and hype in SF lately that keep everyone busy building and/or financially free. Still, I’d be sad if this vibe disappears—it’s been truly helpful to me over the past few years, along with many others.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
